Walter B. Wriston Papers MS134
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Speeches, 1951 -- 2003; 1980 -- 1999; MS134.001; 8.0 Linear Feet; 24 Digital Object(s)
  - Curiouser and Curiouser, American Bankers Association, 1980-10-15; MS134.001.004.00021 (Box 4)
  - Remarks at the American Assembly Award to Reg Jones, 1980-11-19; MS134.001.004.00022 (Box 4)
  - Acceptance Speech for the Citation of Merit from the Salvation Army Association of Greater New York, 1980-12-03; MS134.001.004.00023 (Box 4)
  - The Independent Man and Transference Machine, Lawrence University, 1981-01-15; MS134.001.004.00024 (Box 4)
  - You Can't Tell the Players with a Scorecard, Securities Industry Association Luncheon, 1981-01-21; MS134.001.004.00025 (Box 4)
  - Remarks at Dinner Meeting with the Financial Press, 1981-02-25; MS134.001.004.00026 (Box 4)
  - Going to Hell on a Best-Fit Curve, World Affairs Council, 1981-03-06; MS134.001.004.00027 (Box 4)
  - Introduction of Warren Burger, The Business Council, 1951-05-09 -- 1981-05-07; MS134.001.004.00028 (Box 4)
  - Recycling Revisited, The International Monetary Fund, 1981-06-04; MS134.001.004.00029 (Box 4)
  - Dedication of Citibank South Dakota, Sioux Falls, South Dakota, 1981-06-10; MS134.001.004.00030 (Box 4)
  - Remarks Introducing Edward Seaga, Prime Minister of Jamaica, Edward Seaga Dinner, 1981-06-06; MS134.001.004.00031 (Box 4)
  - The Media, Banking, and the Public Interest, National Press Club, 1981-09-17; MS134.001.004.00032 (Box 4)
  - Introduction of Alexander Haig, The Business Council, 1981-10-09; MS134.001.004.00033 (Box 4)
  - Statement before the Senate Committee on Banking, Housing, and Urban Finances, 1981-10-29; MS134.001.004.00034 (Box 4)
  - Hooray for Hollywood, 1981 Chamber of Commerce Business Conference, 1981-11-10; MS134.001.004.00035 (Box 4)
  - Introduction of Drew Lewis, Secretary of Transportation, Business Council Meeting, 1982-02-10; MS134.001.004.00036 (Box 4)
  - Hooray for Hollywood, Dutch Treat Club, 1982-03-09; MS134.001.004.00037 (Box 4)
  - Remarks at the Correspondent Bankers' Reception, 1982-05-10; MS134.001.004.00038 (Box 4)
  - Remarks at Retirement Dinner for P. Henry Mueller, 1982-06-07; MS134.001.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Remarks at Washington Business Group on Health, 1982-06-23; MS134.001.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Remarks at Spencer/Palmer Retirement, 1982-07-19; MS134.001.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - The Information Society: From Gutenberg to S.W.I.F.T., S.W.I.F.T. Conference SIBOS, 1982-09-23; MS134.001.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - The Scorner's Seat, Boston, Massachusetts, 1982-09-30; MS134.001.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - Remarks at Dinners Club Convention, 1982-10-04; MS134.001.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - Introduction of Caspar W. Weinberger, Secretary of Defense, Business Council Meeting, 1982-10-08; MS134.001.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - Remarks at the Investor Relations Forum, 1982-10-21; MS134.001.005.00008 (Box 5)
  - Looking Backward--Going Forward, Insurance Forum, 1982-11-18; MS134.001.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - An Address at the California Savings and Loan League, 1982-12-08; MS134.001.005.00010 (Box 5)
  - Introduction of William French Smith, U.S. Attorney General, Business Council Meeting, 1983-02-09; MS134.001.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - Remarks at Shearman & Sterling, 1983-01-22 -- 1983-02-24; MS134.001.005.00012; Wriston, Walter B. (Box 5)
    The speech was given January 22, 1983 and it was also given at the New School on February 24, 1983.
    Financial Services Industry; Information technology; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Walter Mitty and Financial Data, SEC [Securities and Exchange Commission] and Financial Reporting Institute University of Southern California, 1983-05-05; MS134.001.005.00013 (Box 5)
  - Testimony before the Subcommittee on Oversight and Investigations of the Committee on Energy and Commerce, 1983-06-28; MS134.001.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - Good News/Bad News/Instant Data, Hong Kong Chamber of Commerce, 1983-10-03; MS134.001.005.00015; Wriston, Walter B. (Box 5)
    Technology; Hong Kong (China); Wriston, Walter B.
  - Bankers and Plato's Cave: Shadow and Substance, American Bankers Association, 1983-10-10; MS134.001.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - A String Bag and the Right Stuff, American Council of Life Insurance, 1983-11-16; MS134.001.005.00017 (Box 5)
  - The Citi of Tomorrow--Today, Bank and Financial Analysts Association, 1984-03-07; MS134.001.005.00018 (Box 5)
  - Remarks in Chicago, Illinois, 1984-03-29; MS134.001.005.00019 (Box 5)
  - The Model of Perpetual Motion and Q&A, Executive Dinner Forum, 1984-05-24; MS134.001.005.00020 (Box 5)
  - Global Recovery and World Debt, International Monetary Conference, 1984-06-04; MS134.001.005.00021 (Box 5)
  - Remarks at Customers Dinner-Edinburgh, 1984-06-09; MS134.001.005.00022 (Box 5)
  - Remarks at Customers Dinner-Guildhall, 1984-06-11; MS134.001.005.00023 (Box 5)
  - Adam and George: 1776 and 1984, Customers Dinner-Merchant Taylors Hall, 1984-06-12; MS134.001.005.00024 (Box 5)
  - Remarks at Customers Lunch-Goldsmiths Hall, 1984-06-13; MS134.001.005.00025 (Box 5)
  - Contemporary Journalism, A Sermon, A Chill Down the Spine, Peat-Marwick Banking Directions Seminar, 1984-09-24; MS134.001.005.00026 (Box 5)
  - Donald Regan Introduction, State Dinner at Lotos Club of New York, 1984-09-11 -- 1984-09-26; MS134.001.005.00027 (Box 5)
  - The Law Business and Business and The Law, The American Bar Association, 1984-10-16 -- 1984-10-31; MS134.001.005.00028 (Box 5)
    The speech was given October 26, 1984.
  - Microseconds and Macropolicy, American Enterprise Institute, 1984-12-06; MS134.001.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - Remarks at the Council of 100 Economics Conference, 1985-01-07; MS134.001.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - Remarks at the Vintage Club Post Election Conference, 1984-10-17 -- 1985-01-16; MS134.001.006.00003 (Box 6)
    The speech was given November 15, 1984.
  - Remarks at MasterCard Conference, 1985-03-01; MS134.001.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - Remarks at the Columbia Business School Dinner, 1985-05-06; MS134.001.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - Gnomons, Words and Policies, The Executive Club, 1985-05-08; MS134.001.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - The Global Marketplace, National Academy of Engineering, 1985-05-14; MS134.001.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - Banking Directions 1985, Peat, Marwick, Mitchell & Co. Symposium, 1984-09-06 -- 1985-06-03; MS134.001.006.00008 (Box 6)
    The speech was given between September 24-25, 1984.
  - Elites, Electrons, and Deregulation, Institutional Investors Conference, 1985-06-14; MS134.001.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - Insights, Consequences and Competition, Sears Sounding Board Ad (Burson-Marsteller), 1975-06-20 -- 1985-10-09; MS134.001.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - You Push the Valve Down, The Fellow of the Academy of International Business, 1984-11-27 -- 1985-10-18; MS134.001.007.00001 (Box 7)
    The speech was given October 18, 1985.
  - Remarks at the Association of American Railroads, 1985-11-05; MS134.001.007.00002 (Box 7)
  - Remarks at the U.S. Savings League, 1985-11-06; MS134.001.007.00003 (Box 7)
  - Never Do Anything For the First Time, Nolan Norton Symposium, 1986-01-26; MS134.001.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - Never Do Anything For the First Time, Health Industry Manufacturers Association, 1986-03-13; MS134.001.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - Remarks at the British Management Institute (Nolan Norton), 1986-04-11; MS134.001.007.00006 (Box 7)
  - Remarks at the Federal Reserve, 1986-05-16; MS134.001.007.00007 (Box 7)
  - Never Do Anything For the First Time, Blue Cross of Greater Philadelphia, 1986-06-04; MS134.001.007.00008 (Box 7)
  - Remarks at GTE [General Telephone and Electronics], 1986-09-16; MS134.001.007.00009 (Box 7)
  - The Information Standard, The Business Council, 1986-10-10; MS134.001.007.00010 (Box 7)
  - Remarks at Policymaker Breakfast Series Trinity University, 1986-10-16; MS134.001.007.00011 (Box 7)
  - Remarks at GTE [General Telephone Electronics] Data Services Corporation, 1986-12-08; MS134.001.008.00001 (Box 8)
  - Remarks at Financial Executives Institute, 1987-03-03; MS134.001.008.00002; Wriston, Walter B. (Box 8)
    Information technology; Technology; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Management and the Information Society, Carnegie Mellon/AMA Awards, 1987-05-19; MS134.001.008.00003 (Box 8)
  - Testimony before the Senate Committee on Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs, (1 of 2), 1986-12-17 -- 1987-06-18; MS134.001.008.00004; Wriston, Walter B. (Box 8)
    The speech was given June 18, 1987.
    Banking law United States; Banks and banking; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Testimony before the Senate Committee on Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs, (2 of 2), 1987-06-09 -- 1987-06-19; MS134.001.008.00005 (Box 8)
  - Remarks at the National Academy of Science, 1987-09-14; MS134.001.008.00006 (Box 8)
  - Remarks at the Prudential Asset Management, 1987-10-14; MS134.001.008.00007 (Box 8)
  - Remarks at the Bear Stearns Financial Industry Conference, 1987-10-15; MS134.001.008.00008 (Box 8)
    Also given at the Business Council Meeting on October 10, 1986
  - Remarks at the National Association of Service Retailers, 1987-10-23; MS134.001.008.00009; Wriston, Walter B. (Box 8)
    Business; Information technology; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Remarks at the Annual Lawyers Dinner, 1987-11-30; MS134.001.008.00010 (Box 8)
  - Remarks at the Digital Conference, 1987-12-02; MS134.001.008.00011 (Box 8)
  - The Silent, Noisy Revolution: Foreign Policy in the Information Age, The Council on Foreign Relations, 1988-02-05 -- 1988-03-16; MS134.001.009.00001 (Box 9)
    The speech was given March 16, 1988.
  - Yesterday's Vocabulary, Today's World, Western Association of Food Chains, 1988-04-11; MS134.001.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - Remarks at the Bilderberg Meeting, 1988-06-03; MS134.001.009.00003 (Box 9)
  - Remarks at the International Institute of Communications, 1988-09-13; MS134.001.009.00004; Wriston, Walter B. (Box 9)
  - Remarks at the Norton-Nolan Symposium, 1988-09-19; MS134.001.009.00005; Wriston, Walter B. (Box 9)
  - Remarks at MCI, 1988-10-03; MS134.001.009.00006 (Box 9)
  - Remarks at the Business Council, 1988-10-08; MS134.001.009.00007; Wriston, Walter B. (Box 9)
    Budget deficits United States; United States Economic Policy; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Remarks at the Open Dining Club British Management Institute, 1987-07-08 -- 1988-11-22; MS134.001.009.00008 (Box 9)
    The speech was given November 9, 1988.
  - Remarks at the Chemical Specialties Manufacturer's Association, 1988-12-05; MS134.001.009.00009 (Box 9)
  - New Wine in Old Bottles, Indiana University School of Business, 1989-04-07 -- 1989-04-25; MS134.001.009.00010; Wriston, Walter B. (Box 9)
    The speech was given April 18, 1989.
    Economics.; Information technology; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Doing Business In the Information Age, DMA [Direct Marketing Association] Annual Financial Service Conference, 1989-06-08; MS134.001.009.00011; Wriston, Walter B. (Box 9)
    There is an audio CD of this speech in Series 4, box 30, and item #00005.
  - Remarks at the SIM Conference (Coca Cola Company Georgia State University), 1989-09-25; MS134.001.010.00001 (Box 10)
  - Rupert Murdock Introduction, 1989-11-09; MS134.001.010.00002 (Box 10)
  - Remarks at Casualty Actuarial Society, 1989-11-14; MS134.001.010.00003; Wriston, Walter B. (Box 10)
  - The Day the (Electronic) World Stopped: June 28, 1974, 1990; MS134.001.010.00004 (Box 10)
  - New Trends and Old Economics, Forum Club of Collier County, 1991-03-01 -- 1991-03-11; MS134.001.010.00005 (Box 10)
    This speech was given March 1, 1991.
  - Remarks at the Sons of the Revolution Patriot Award Dinner, 1992-02-21; MS134.001.010.00006 (Box 10)
  - Twilight of Sovereignty, The Royal Society for the Encouragement of Arts, Manufacturers and Commerce, (1 of 2), 1991-11-12 -- 1992-03-09; MS134.001.010.00007 (Box 10)
    The speech was given March 9, 1992.
  - Twilight of Sovereignty, The Royal Society for the Encouragement of Arts, Manufacturers and Commerce, (2 of 2), 1992-03-09 -- 1992-06-20; MS134.001.010.00008 (Box 10)
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty, The Commonwealth Club, (1 of 2), 1992-11-05 -- 1992-11-10; MS134.001.010.00009 (Box 10)
    The speech was given November 10, 1992. A DVD of the speech is in Series 4, box 30, and item #00007.
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty, The Commonwealth Club, (2 of 2), 1992-11-10 -- 1992-12-04; MS134.001.010.00010; Wriston, Walter B. (Box 10)
  - Kathryn C. Spencer Memorial Tribute, 1992; MS134.001.010.00011 (Box 10)
    Kathryn C. Spencer died on December 18, 1992.
  - Remarks at BENS [Business Executives for National Security], 1993-01-12 -- 1993-01-19; MS134.001.010.00012 (Box 10)
    The speech was given January 14, 1993.
  - Clintonomics: The Information Revolution and the New Global Market Economy, Independent Policy Forum, (1 of 2), 1992-11-25 -- 1993-01-25; MS134.001.011.00001 (Box 11)
    The speech was given January 25, 1993.
  - Clintonomics: The Information Revolution and the New Global Market Economy, Independent Policy Forum, (2 of 2), 1993-01-25; MS134.001.011.00002 (Box 11)
  - Remarks at Professor Brian Quinn's Seminar, Dartmouth College, (1 of 2), 1993-04-19 -- 1993-04-20; MS134.001.011.00003 (Box 11)
    The speech was given April 20, 1993.
  - Remarks at Professor Brian Quinn's Seminar, Dartmouth College, (2 of 2), 1993-04-20; MS134.001.011.00004 (Box 11)
  - Mistress of the World, The Freedom Forum-Media Studies Center, 1993-09-08 -- 1993-11-02; MS134.001.011.00005 (Box 11)
    The speech was given October 25, 1993.
  - Techno-Tinkering vs. Real Revolution, The University Club, 1994-02-02 -- 1994-03-02; MS134.001.011.00006 (Box 11)
    The speech was given March 2, 1994.
  - Techno-Tinkering vs. Real Revolution, Chamber of Commerce, 1994-03-21 -- 1994-03-29; MS134.001.011.00007 (Box 11)
    The speech was given March 21, 1994.
  - Remarks at the Arthur Anderson Conference, (1 of 2), 1994-05-16 -- 1994-06-01; MS134.001.011.00008 (Box 11)
    The speech was given June 1, 1994.
  - Remarks at the Arthur Anderson Conference, (2 of 2), 1994-06-01 -- 1994-06-30; MS134.001.012.00001 (Box 12)
  - The Future is Unbelievable, Barclays Executive Program, 1994-06-29 -- 1994-09-20; MS134.001.012.00002 (Box 12)
    The speech was given September 20, 1994.
  - The Busiest Corner in the World, Tandem Finance Industry Forum, (1 of 2), 1995-01-13 -- 1995-01-20; MS134.001.012.00003 (Box 12)
    The speech was given between January 17-20, 1995.
  - The Busiest Corner in the World, Tandem Finance Industry Forum, (2 of 2), 1995-01-17 -- 1995-01-20; MS134.001.012.00004 (Box 12)
  - The Future is Unbelievable, University of Texas at San Antonio, 1995-01-24 -- 1995-02-09; MS134.001.012.00005 (Box 12)
    The speech was given February 9, 1995.
  - The Future is Unbelievable, The Pacific Institute, (1 of 2), 1995-05-25 -- 1995-07-31; MS134.001.012.00006 (Box 12)
    The speech was given August 10, 1995.
  - The Future is Unbelievable, The Pacific Institute, (2 of 2), 1995-08-10; MS134.001.012.00007 (Box 12)
  - The Whiskey Ain't Working Anymore, Perspective 95, (1 of 2), 1995-09-12; MS134.001.012.00008 (Box 12)
    The speech was given September 14, 1995.
  - The Whiskey Ain't Working Anymore, Perspective 95, (2 of 2), 1995-09-14; MS134.001.013.00001 (Box 13)
  - Remarks at New York Hospital, 1996-01-22; MS134.001.013.00002 (Box 13)
    Computer printout of a draft
  - Money-Back to the Future?, Claremont McKenna College, 1996-11-06 -- 1996-11-20; MS134.001.013.00003 (Box 13)
    The speech was given November 20, 1996. There is a DVD of the speech in Series 4, box 31, and item #00011.
  - Bits, Bytes, Politics and Power, Res Publica Society Claremont McKenna College, 1996-10-01 -- 1996-11-21; MS134.001.013.00004 (Box 13)
    The speech was given November 21, 1996.
  - Bits, Bytes, Peace & Diplomacy, United States Institute of Peace, (1 of 2), 1997-03-27; MS134.001.013.00005 (Box 13)
    The speech was given April 1, 1997.
  - Bits, Bytes, Power & Diplomacy, United States Institute of Peace, (2 of 2), 1997-04-01 -- 1997-06; MS134.001.013.00006 (Box 13)
  - Dumb Networks and Smart Capital, Cato Institute 15th Annual Monetary Conference, 1997-10-14 -- 1998-03-17; MS134.001.013.00007 (Box 13)
    The speech was given October 14, 1997.
  - Shearman & Sterling and Citibank Yesterday and Tomorrow, Boca Raton Resort and Club, 1998-04-24; MS134.001.013.00008 (Box 13)
  - IMF [International Monetary Fund], G.E. [General Electric] International Meeting, 1998-04 -- 1998-06-19; MS134.001.013.00009 (Box 13)
    The speech was given June 19, 1998
  - Two Lucky People, Rose and Milton Friedman Dinner, 1998-07-02 -- 1998-08-20; MS134.001.014.00001 (Box 14)
    The speech was given July 22, 1998.
  - Rules for a Wired World, Manhattan Institute for Policy Research, 1998-10-06 -- 1998-11-23; MS134.001.014.00002 (Box 14)
    The speech was given October 6, 1998.
  - Introduction of Bill Gates, Manhattan Institute Lunch, 1998-12-02; MS134.001.014.00003 (Box 14)
  - Shadow and Reality: The Quick and the Dead, Fortune Financial Services Technology Forum, 1999-03-04; MS134.001.014.00004 (Box 14)
  - Remarks at the Media Lab-Vanguard, 1999-05-17; MS134.001.014.00005 (Box 14)
  - Quarantine, The 1999 Forbes CEO Forum, 1999-06-25; MS134.001.014.00006 (Box 14)
  - The Technology of Freedom, The Mont Pelerin Society, 1999-08-29 -- 1999-09-20; MS134.001.014.00007 (Box 14)
    The speech was given between August 29-September 1, 1999.
  - The Future is Unbelievable, Citibank, 1999-11-18; MS134.001.014.00008 (Box 14)
  - The Future is Unbelievable, The Federal Reserve Bank of Cleveland, 1999-12-08; MS134.001.014.00009 (Box 14)
  - Notes for Reuters Forum, 2000-01-26; MS134.001.014.00010 (Box 14)
  - Remarks at George S. Moore Memorial Service, 2000-05-22; MS134.001.014.00011 (Box 14)
  - The Great Disconnect: Balance Sheets vs. Market Value, Cap Gemini Ernst & Young Center for Business Innovations Conference, 2000-09-06 -- 2000-10-02; MS134.001.014.00012 (Box 14)
    The speech was given October 2, 2000.
  - William Spencer Memorial Service, 2001-09-13; MS134.001.014.00013 (Box 14)
  - Introduction for Dr. Herbert Pardes, 2002-04-09; MS134.001.014.00014 (Box 14)
  - Fletcher in the Information Age, Convocation Speech at the Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy at Tufts University, (1 of 2), 2003-06-18 -- 2003-08-29; MS134.001.015.00001 (Box 15)
    The speech was given September 3, 2003. There is a DVD of Walter Wriston speech in Series 4, box 31, item #00015, and bar code: 39090014010363.
  - Fletcher in the Information Age, Convocation Speech at the Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy at Tufts University, (2 of 2), 2003-06-18 -- 2003-09-03; MS134.001.015.00002 (Box 15)
  - List of Speeches and Articles, 1962 -- 2000; MS134.001.015.00003 (Box 15)
  - If You Ask Me: A Global Banker Reflects on Our Times, 1980; MS134.001.015.00004 (Box 15)
    This work was sent at later date, on September 13, 2007.
  - Remarks at the Committee to Study Computer Technology and Service Sector Productivity (1 of 2), 1991-05-20 -- 1991-06-11; MS134.001.015.00005 (Box 15)
    This work was sent at later date on December 4, 2007 (Accession Number: 2008.035).
  - Remarks at the Committee to Study Computer Technology and Service Sector Productivity (2 of 2), 1991-05-20 -- 1991-06-11; MS134.001.015.00006 (Box 15)
  - [Kathryn C. Spencer Memorial Tribute] Spencer, 1992; MS134.001.038.00001 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] California Speech, 1992-11-10; MS134.001.038.00002 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] California Speech, 1992-11-10; MS134.001.038.00003 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Twilight of Sovereignty] California Speech 2, 1992-11-10; MS134.001.038.00004 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Clintonomics] California Speech and alternate, 1992-11-10; MS134.001.038.00005 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Clintonomics] Independent Institute, 1993-01-25; MS134.001.038.00006 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Clintonomics] Independent Institute, 1993-01-18 -- 1993-01-25; MS134.001.038.00007 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Clintonomics] Independent Institute, 1993-01-25; MS134.001.038.00008 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - Bens, 1993-01-12 -- 1993-01-19; MS134.001.038.00009 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - BENS, 1993-01-12; MS134.001.038.00010 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
    January 12-19, 1993.
  - BENS, 1993-01-19; MS134.001.038.00011 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Remarks at Professor Brian Quinn's Seminar, Dartmouth College] Dartmouth, 1993-04-19 -- 1993-04-20; MS134.001.038.00012 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Remarks at Professor Brian Quinn's Seminar, Dartmouth College] Dartmouth, 1993-04-19 -- 1993-04-20; MS134.001.038.00013 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Mistress of the World] Media, 1993-10-25; MS134.001.038.00014 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Mistress of the World] Media Studies Center, 1993-10-25; MS134.001.038.00015 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - Chicago Speech, 1994; MS134.001.038.00016 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Techno-Tinkering vs. Real Revolution] University Club Speech, 1994-03-02; MS134.001.038.00017 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - Arthur Anderson [conference], 1994-06-01; MS134.001.038.00018 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Arthur Anderson conference] Arthus Anderson, 1994-06-01; MS134.001.038.00019 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [The Future is Unbelievable drafts] Barclays, 1994-09-20; MS134.001.038.00020 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [The Busiest Corner of the World] Tandem Speech, 1995-01-17 -- 1995-01-20; MS134.001.038.00021 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [The Busiest Corner of the World] Tandem Speech, 1995-01-17 -- 1995-01-20; MS134.001.038.00022 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [The Future is Unbelievable] Texas University Speech, 1995-02-09; MS134.001.038.00023 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [The Future is Unbelievable] Texas University Speech, 1995-02-09; MS134.001.038.00024 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [The Future is Unbelievable] Pacific Research Institute, 1995-08-10; MS134.001.038.00025 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [The Whiskey Ain't Working Anymore] The whiskey ain't working anymo, 1995-09-14; MS134.001.038.00026 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - New York hospital, 1996-01-22; MS134.001.038.00027 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Money- Back to the Future?] Smart Card, 1996-11-20; MS134.001.038.00028 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Bits, Bytes, Politics and Power] Bits, Bytes and Politics, 1996-11-21; MS134.001.038.00029 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - Bits, Bytes, Peace and Diplomacy, 1997-04-01; MS134.001.038.00030 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Dumb Networks and Small Capital] Cato, 1997-10-14; MS134.001.038.00031 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Shearman and Sterling and Citibank Yesterday and Tomorrow] S and S, 1998-04-24; MS134.001.038.00032 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
    The original document title for 'S and S' is 'S & S'.
  - IMF, 1998-06-19; MS134.001.038.00033 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Two Lucky People] Milton, 1998-07-22; MS134.001.038.00034 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Two Lucky People, Rose and Milton Friedman Dinner] Milton, 1998-07-22; MS134.001.038.00035 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Two Lucky People, Rose and Milton Friedman Dinner] Milton2, 1998-07-22; MS134.001.038.00036 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Rules for a Wired World] Manhattan, 1998-10-06; MS134.001.038.00037 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Introduction of Bill Gates] Bill Gates, 1998-12-02; MS134.001.038.00038 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Shadow and Reality] The Quick and the Dead, 1999-03-04; MS134.001.038.00039 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [The Technology of Freedom] Vanguard, 1999-05-17; MS134.001.038.00040 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Quarantine] Atlanta, 1999-06-25; MS134.001.038.00041 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [The Future is Unbelievable] Money, 1999-11-18; MS134.001.038.00042 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [The Future is Unbelievable] University Club Speech, 1999-12-08; MS134.001.038.00043 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [The Future is Unbelievable] University Club Speech2, 1999-12-08; MS134.001.038.00044 (Box MS134 Shared 1)
  - [Remarks at George S. Moore Memorial Service] Uncle George, 2000-05-22; MS134.001.038.00045 (Box MS134 Shared 1)